# Systems engineer / Software developer Yeison Betancourt Solis C.C 1.115.080.936 Buga - Valle 25 Years old





PHONE

(+57) 316 279 3738



EMAIL

yeisonbe10@hotmail.com



WEBSITE

<u>Portafolio</u>



LINKEDIN Perfil

## **Profile**

I'm a FullStack developer from Valle University with four years of experience in software development for the technology sector. I'm looking to collaborate in a position as an application developer since I have experience in different web and mobile projects.

I have skills for cooperative and team work, I'm proactive, responsible and with fast learning ability. Interested in the development of web applications, mobile app and project management.

# **Professional Experiences**

□ September - Present

### **Software Engineer**

Fullstack Labs +57 (5) 385-1980

Development for web and mobile with international clients projects

☐ February 2019 - September 2019

**Development Engineer** 

CETOCO SAS 3187348993

Development for web and mobile applications

☐ August 2016 - February 2019

## **Development Engineer**

ADATEC

3707777

Development and implementation for web and mobile applications

## □ September 2015 – August 2016

### **Development Engineer**

ARQUITECSOFT 3797724

Development and implementation of the new requirements requested for the application

## **Education**

□ 2016

## **Information Systems Engineering**

VALLE UNIVERSITY - CALI

8. Semester - August - December 2014

**2010** 

## **Secondary education**

TULIO ENRIQUE TASCÓN - BUGA

# **Engineering Stacks**

### PROGRAMMING:

ES6, JavaScript, TypeScript, React, React Native, Redux, C#, C++, PHP, .NET

#### FRAMEWORKS:

Angular, Ionic, AngularJS, Vue, NodeJS, Visual Studio, YII, Laravel, JDeveloper, Yeoman, Joomla, Wordpress, **PrestaShop** 

#### **VERSION CONTROL:**

Git, Bitbucket, SVN

### KNOWI FDGF:

Movil, Frontend, Backend, relational databases. non-relational databases

### **HOBBIES**



## COURSES

- English (High intermediate B1+) Centro Cultural Colombo Americano
- React JS + redux + ES6 Udemy
- Vue JS + Firebase Udemy
- Angular Udemy
- Information security Icesi University
- Basic Programming Platzi
- Programming Websites with HTML and JAVASCRIPT Sena Virtual
- Computer Design of databases in SQL Sena Virtual
- Computer architecture Sena Virtual
- C++ Sena Virtual
- MicrosoftOffice and OpenOffice

# **Projects**

- Portfolio Web with GitHub Pages http://betancourtyeison.github.io/
- Angular applications
- Vue JS applications
- React applications
- Websites with Responsive Design
- Java applications like Sodoku and LunarLand
- Refrastrabe company Guacari Valle <a href="http://refrastrabe.com/">http://refrastrabe.com/</a>
- Refratek company http://refratek.com/

# **Experiences**

- With python + django I have created an app had to save all the data from different companies like their employees, orders, polls and more things and these information were used to be displayed in a CMS and application
- With MySQL I had to create the gueries that we needed to get data like the orders that were for some specific users.
- With reactis I have created a crud to save the info of a hospital connecting Firebase and other technologies.
- With react native I have created an application like an e-commerce to buy different products using a wallet that is recharged with payment methods and one more thing is that I used typescript in that project
- Years of experiences with Python: 2-3 years
- Years of experiences with Node and NoSQL: 4 years
- Years of experiences with React and React Native: 4 years

## References

Name: Juan Carlos Renteria Company: Refrastrabe S.A.S.

Job title: Director Phone: 310 836 0100

Name: Oscar Fernando Betancourt

Company: CVC - Corporación autónoma regional del valle del cauca

Job title: Systems analyst Phone: 322 613 2940

Name: Jorge Arley Castaño Company: Su Red

Job title: Development engineer

Phone: 315 555 4340

